# ANAS BESMAR .NET DEVELOPER

Midan -Damascus- Syria Mobile +963-938350459

Email: anas.bsr.2000@gmail.com

I am 24 years old I obtained a software engineering degree from the Computer Technical Institute in Damascus, and information technology with a specialization in information systems from the Syrian Virtual University, and I aspire to increase my experience and strive to contribute to the development of the company I am in by developing myself.

## WORK EXPERIENCE

#### 09/2023 - PRESENT

#### IT MANAGEMENT, AL NADA DEVELOPMENT NGO

- Modification of the project code for the charity website.
- Database administrator.
- Work on analyzing the problems of the charity website.
- Monitoring and supervising the entered system data.
- Providing technical support for the systems and networks available in the centers.
- Provide protection and secure backup for devices in the charity.
- Dealing with suppliers and merchants to purchase charity supplies.

#### 07/2022 - 08/2023

## IT ASSISTANT, AL NADA DEVELOPMENT NGO

- Providing technical support for the systems and networks available in the centers.
- Database administrator.
- Work on analyzing the problems of the charity website.
- Monitoring and supervising the entered system data.

#### **EDUCATION**

#### **2021 – PRESENT**

Bachelor's in information technology (BAIT). Syrian virtual university, Damascus –Syria

## 2019 - 2021

Software engineering

University of Damascus, Technical computer college

#### **SKILLS**

- Good experience in a programming language C#.
- Good experience in C# ASP.NET CORE
- Good experience in C# ASP.NET MVC
- Ability to work with databases Oracle, SQL Server, MySQL Workbench.

- Excellent knowledge of Entity Framework, and Entity Framework core.
- Intermediate experience in web design languages HTML,CSS,JavaScript,BootStrap
- Ability to work with code.

- Programming windows applications using (WindowsForm, WPF).
- Good programmatic thinking for problem solving.

# **CERTIFICATIONS**

- Holds a certificate in MCSA Server, MCSA Client.
- Certificate in C# (https://www.rwaq.org/).
- Certificate in HTML, CSS (https://www.rwaq.org/).

## **PROJECTS**

- Graduation project website: a website for selling and managing clothes, and it includes two
  accounts for the merchant and the customer.
   (Asp.NET MVC, SQLSERVER, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, BootStrap)
- A website similar to WhatsApp : a website where you log in and talk to several different accounts.
  - (ASP.NET MVC, SQLSERVER, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, AJAX, JQUERY)
- Desktop application: an application in which all universities, majors and subjects are dealt
  with and managed, and audio and video lectures are added.
   (WPF C#, SQLSERVER, Matrial UI).